

Artiom Manokhin Kharkiv, Ukraine

Email: <u>amanokhin22@gmail.com</u> Phone: +38 (099)-461-54-38

Social: linkedin.com/in/artiom-manokhin

Credly: https://www.credly.com/users/artiom-manokhin

GitHub: github.com/amanokhin22

Summary

Trained front-end developer with over 2000 hours of training and working on pet projects. Ready to go with a modern set of tools such as Git, Jira, Redux toolkit, Next JS etc. Passionate about frontend and web development in general. Motivated to learn and improve skills both independently and in practice. Ready to work on ReactJS or related technology. Experienced in communicating with clients and the team to solve business problems.

Technology Stack

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Redux
- NextJS
- React Hooks
- React Router

- Material UI
- Bootstrap
- Class Components
- CSS/SASS
- HTML
- Modular CSS
- Nodejs / webpack
- MS Excel
- Redux/toolkit
- REST API
- JSON Server
- Axios
- GIT/GitHub, Vercel
- Jira

Career Highlights

- Successfully completed 10 education projects
- Over 2000 hours of web development learning
- Trained more than 20 newbies at a previous job
- Hungry for knowledge, got certified in cybersecurity
- Analysis and presentation of results in the form of reports on 20+ pages and 20+ slides
- Decomposition of requirements and delegation to a team of 7 people

Certifications

• CISCO Certified - Introduction to Cybersecurity

Languages

English: intermediate

Ukraine: fluent Russian: fluent

Education

Maksym Hrom, Mentorship program

Junior Frontend, React Developer Program

Apr 2022 - present

- HTML/CSS/JS basics and practice 200 hours
- JSON server, REST API, Axios 100 hours
- React JS, class components, functional components, old Redux 300 hours
- TypeScript, React Hooks, Redux Toolkit, modern Redux 200 hours
- Next JS simple project 100 hours
- React basic patterns, Authorisation, RegEx, Date Manipulation 100 h

Contact: Maksym Hrom - linkedin.com/in/maksym-hrom/

Internship at Lambda Team https://lambda.direct/

Junior Frontend, React Developer Program https://tinvio-serverless-academy-n3t3bvxuu-amanokhin22.vercel.app/ Jan 2023 – Mar 2023

- HTML/CSS/JS basics and practice
- React JS, functional components
- TypeScript, React Hooks, Telegram-bots, API

Yaroslav Mudryi National Law University (Kharkiv)

Master's Degree, Lawyer September 2010 - June 2011

Experience

Lawyer

Self-employed, full-time Mar 2019 - Aug 2022 Kharkiv, Ukraine

- Communication with clients
- Problem solving
- Deep analysis of the client's business
- Develop a team and regulation processes in the team (3-7 members)
- Presentation in powerpoint and calculation in MS Excel

Used: MS Excel, MS Powerpoint, MS Word, cloud storage, backup, ZIP

Public service

full-time

Aug 2011 - Feb 2019

Kharkiv, Ukraine

- Work as a part of a team (20-30 members)
- Presentation of results of work (40+ pages reports, and 15+ slides)
- Mentoring a newcomers and delegation work (mentored 20+ newcomers)

Used: MS Excel, MS Powerpoint, MS Word